/*************************************************
**
** You're viewing a file in the SMAPI mod dump, which contains a copy of every open-source SMAPI mod
** for queries and analysis.
**
** This is *not* the original file, and not necessarily the latest version.
** Source repository: https://github.com/poohnhi/PoohCore
**
*************************************************/

{
    // Perms get: Dodo, Lemur, Bagi, Nova, Mads, Desty, Squeaks
    "Changes": [
        // Base ES
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Aideen"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Aideen loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Aideen {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{AideenFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Aideen {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Beatrice"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Beatrice loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Beatrice {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Eloise"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Eloise loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eloise {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Jacob Vivienne
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Eloise loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Eloise 1 2 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eloise {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{EloiseFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Eloise 1 2 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eloise {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Eyvinder"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonalNegative.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Eyvinder loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eyvinder {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"

                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Jacob"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jacob loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jacob {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Eloise Vivienne
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jacob loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Jacob 1 2 3 4 5, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jacob {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{JacobFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Jacob 1 5 1 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jacob {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["JosephineK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:JosephineK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current JosephineK {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Oliver
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:JosephineK loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current JosephineK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }, 
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "57873000",
                "HasSeenEvent |contains=57873005": false
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["KatarynaLK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:KatarynaLK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current KatarynaLK {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasFlag": "KatarynaBecomesSocial"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Leximonster"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leximonster loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Leximonster {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:OliverK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Leximonster {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}, PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Any 57872011"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["OliverK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:OliverK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current OliverK {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Josephine
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:OliverK loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "ANY \"SYNCED_CHOICE day OliverK 1 2 1\" \"!PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Any 57872011\", PLAYER_HEARTS Current OliverK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}, !PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Host 57873005"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leximonster loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "ANY \"SYNCED_CHOICE day OliverK 1 2 2\" \"PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Host 57873005\", PLAYER_HEARTS Current OliverK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}, PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Any 57872011"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "57873000"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Rosa"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Rosa loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Rosa {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{RosaFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Rosa {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["ToriLK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:ToriLK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current ToriLK {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{ToriLKFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current ToriLK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["VivienneLK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:VivienneLK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current VivienneLK {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:VivienneLK loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current VivienneLK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "57875000"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["LumaJunimo"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:LumaJunimo loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current LumaJunimo {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        // Dodo
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["RodneyOBrien"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:RodneyOBrien loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current RodneyOBrien {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Friends Gus, Gunther, Leah, Elliott. When his relatives are released add a family field
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{RodneyOBrienFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current RodneyOBrien {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasMod": "TheFrenchDodo.RodneyOBrien"
            }
        },
        // Bagi
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Nora"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Nora loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nora {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Friends Maru Harvey Tori Eli Dylan
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{NoraFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nora {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasMod": "Bagi.Nora.CP"
            }
        },
        // Nova
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Nova.Eli"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Nova.Eli loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nova.Eli {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Dylan, Leah, Elliott, Emily (straight from friend and family)
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Nova.Eli loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Nova.Eli 1 10 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nova.Eli {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Abigail (after adventurer guild event), Krobus (after player get access to sewer), Mateo (after player meet them in the mine), Eve, Nora, Sen (after deep woods event), Cirrus (after her introduction event) and all of Bearfam
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{Nova.EliFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Nova.Eli 1 10 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nova.Eli {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasMod": "TenebrousNova.EliDylan.CP"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Nova.Dylan"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Nova.Dylan loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nova.Dylan {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Eli, Leah, Elliott, Willy, and if Nova update, Maru and Demetrius (straight from friend and family)
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Nova.Dylan loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Nova.Dylan 1 10 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nova.Dylan {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                // Friends EveT, Nora, Cirrus, Gudrun Gunnar Sondra Teren Sigurd (50%)
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{Nova.DylanFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Nova.Dylan 1 10 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Nova.Dylan {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasMod": "TenebrousNova.EliDylan.CP"
            }
        },
        // Desty
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Mateo"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Mateo loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Mateo {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Krobus (after player get access to sewer), Eli
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{MateoFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Mateo 1 10 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Mateo {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasMod": "DN.SnS"
            }
        },
    ]
}